嘿 我的钱包他偷了我的钱包
Hey  My purse  He's got my purse
嘿 拦住他 不是吧
Hey, stop him   Come on.
来人拦住他他偷了我的钱包
Somebody stop him  He's got my purse
警察不许动
Police  Freeze
嘿 站住别挡路
Hey  Stop  Out of my way
别挡路让开警察
Get out of my way  Out of my way  Police
让开
Move
你小子不会是下去了吧
You did not just go down there...
什么鬼
What the fuck
什么破事
Fuck sakes.
把你的手举起来
Get your fucking hands in the air
我不会再说第二遍了混蛋
I ain't gonna say it again, motherfucker
见鬼
Fuck.
你好保斯维克警探
Hello, Detective Bozwick.
我想和你玩个游戏不
I want to play a game.  No
两分钟后三号线列车就要开过来了
The 3 train is arriving in two minutes.
由你决定
It is up to you to decide
这是不是你人生中的最后一站
if this will be your final stop.
你曾多次扮演目击者
You have taken the witness stand many times,
用你的谎言轻易制裁无辜的人们
and railroaded innocent people with your lies,
把他们送入监狱
putting them away in jail.
今天你将要受到制裁
Today, it is you who will be railroaded.
你有一个活下去的机会
You have one chance to live.
你那经常用来撒谎
Tear from your mouth the tongue that has so often been used
的舌头现在是关键
to lie and to deceive.
纵身一跃即可活命
Take a leap of faith, and you will live.
只有你自身的重量能扯断
Only your weight will rip away
你满是谎言的舌头保你一命
your lying tongue and save you.
是生是死做出选择吧
Live or die, make your choice.
《电锯惊魂9：漩涡》
你在说什么那部电影获了很多奖
What you talking about  That movie won awards.
你知道的汤姆汉克斯可不是什么好家伙
You know, Tom Hanks is a straight pimp, man,
但是我怀疑现在还能拍出这种电影么
but I don't know if you could make that movie today.
你在扯什么东西呢
What the fuck you going on about
特殊需求虐待 特殊需求?
Special needs abuse. Special needs
怎么你开悟了不是开悟
What, you woke now Not woke,
但是你不能叫别人残废也不能骂别人发育迟钝
but you can't say "handicapped," you can't say "retarded."
你得说他们情况特殊我试着放尊重了
You got to say "special needs," I'm trying to be respectful.
阿甘就是个有特殊需求的人
Forrest Gump was special needs, man.
那个女主角叫什么?
What was the name of the girl
珍妮珍妮
Jenny.  Jenny.
他做的一切都是为了珍妮
He did everything for Jenny.
这个混蛋做了许多不得了的事
This motherfucker did some shit.
他进行了横穿全国的慢跑
He jogged across the whole country.
他打乒乓球击败了中国队
He beat China in pingpong.
你知道这有多困难吗
You know how fucking hard that shit is
他是个战争英雄
He was a war hero.
谁能比阿甘更厉害?
Who the fuck is nicer than Forrest Gump
他最好的朋友
His best friend
一个是黑人另一个是失去双腿的白人
was a nigga and a white boy with no legs.
他通过捕虾成为了亿万富翁
He made a billion dollars selling shrimp.
而她仍然不肯和阿甘睡觉
And she still wouldn't fuck him.
嘿 最终他们在一起了
Hey, eventually, they got together.
是在女主角得了艾滋病之后
Yeah, after she got AIDS.
她一得了艾滋病就开始勾引阿甘
As soon as she got AIDS, she's like, "Hey, Forrest..."
快滚吧兄弟
Get the fuck out of here, man.
让他也感染了艾滋病?
Giving that guy AIDS
你在开玩笑嘛 是
Are you kidding me   Yeah.
那个混蛋真的该骂 但是他没有感染
That shit's abusive.  But he ain't get it.
我可没看到续集出来《阿甘正传》第二部呢
I ain't see no sequel. Where's Gump 2
嘿 里科刚从电梯里出来
Yo, Rico just got off the elevator.
哦 糟了
Oh, shit.
开千吧
Let's do this.
趴下趴下立刻
Get down  Get down right now
现在趴下现在给我趴下
Get down right now  You know what this is
你知道我们在干什么
You know what this is
这就对了都放进来快点
That's right  Put it all  Come on  Down
塞满这个包都给我放到包里
Fill up this bag  Put it in the motherfucking bag
快点
Come on.
你知道该怎么样 安静
You know what to do   Chill
后退
Get back
我想要可卡因我想要钱
I want that coke  I want that money
我想要一切
I want everything
靠
Shit.
九十秒我们得走了
Ninety seconds, we gotta go
警察不许动
Freeze  Police
举起手来把手举起来
Hands up  Get your hands up
下车都给我下来
Get out of the car. Get the fuck out of...
泽克是你吗
Zeke  Is that you
泽克
Zeke
你在搞什么
What the fuck is wrong with you
你在做潜伏任务
You do an undercover op...
你不明白吗这事儿没法协调
You don't clear it, there's no coordination.
我们可是重案组
We are Homicide,
你却在旅馆里忙着打劫毒品贩子
but you're robbing drug dealers in a fucking hotel.
我这里接到一堆报警电话
I had a dozen 911 calls come in.
要是有人被杀了怎么办
What if someone got killed
那个团伙上周杀了四个人我们抓住了那帮人
That crew killed four people last week, and we got them.
要是我的身份没有暴露还能抓住更多
And we could have got more of them if my cover wasn't blown.
去你妈的身份泽克
Fuck your cover, Zeke
你还和以前一样独自行动没有后援什么也没有
You were off on your own, as usual, no backup, nothing.
没有后援因为在警局里
No backup, 'cause there's nobody on the force
没有我能信任的人
I can fucking trust
现在开始你要学会团队合作
From now on, you're going to learn to be a team player.
你将会得到一个搭档珍妮把申克叫进来
You're getting a partner. Jeannie, send Schenk in.
我看起来像个带小孩的保姆吗?
Do I look like a fucking Jamaican nanny
我是乐意收拾烂摊子的人吗?不可能
Do I smell like jerk sauce and baby wipes  No
我不需要任何搭档
Me no want no partner
我才不会去照顾哪个混球
I'm not babysitting some fucking rook.
不你必须
Yes, you are.
你的老爸是大领导马库斯·班克斯
Just because your dad was Chief fucking Marcus Banks
并不意味着你就能不服从管理
doesn't mean you get out of the shit.
别提我的父亲行吗
Stop making this about my father, okay
他已经离职了你现在才是部门的老大
He's gone, you're the head of the department now.
是啊 戏精
Yeah. Drama queen.
泽克已经过去12年了
Zeke, it's been 12 years.
是啊 整整12年
Yes  Twelve fucking years.
12年前我揭发了一名黑警察
Twelve years ago, I turned in a dirty cop,
我因此获得了一枚奖章办了一件大案
I get a medal for it. Big fucking deal
同样我也中了一发子弹
I also got a bullet,
所以在我以后的职业生涯中我都得时刻注意背后暗箭
and I got to look over my back for the rest of my career.
闭嘴
Shut up
听你鬼扯这些东西
It is too fucking hot in here
真他妈的让我火大
for me to listen to this bullshit.
我有棘手的事情要办
I got a heat wave going on.
我们得实行封锁
We got rolling blackouts,
这座城市要疯了停
the city is nuts. Stop
队长你要见我?
You wanted to see me, Captain
是的进来
Yeah, come in.
泽克见见我们的见习警探
Zeke, I want you to meet
威廉·申克
Detective in training, William Schenk.
他是警察学院拔尖的人才你别把这事搞砸了
He was the top of his academy, so don't screw this up.
泽克将会指导你训练你
Zeke is going to break you in, show you the ropes.
班克斯警探很高兴
Detective Banks, it's good to...
好吧
Yup...
走啊好的
Go.  Okay.
哈里斯警官1 0 3
Officer Harris, 103.
警佐琼斯到前台来
Sergeant Jones, front desk.
所以你早上一般喝什么咖啡
So, uh... How do you take your coffee in the morning
要你管
Alone.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 我懂了
Hey, man, I get it.
换做我也不想跟一个陌生新人捆在一起
I wouldn't want to be stuck with some random kid either.
你不想和我做搭档
You don't want to be my partner.
你不明白
You don't know that.
你的父亲是我在这的原因
Your dad's the reason for all of this.
他是我一开始想成为警察的原因
He's why I wanted to do this in the first place.
然而我不是他
And I'm not him.
做好失望的准备吧
Prepare to be underwhelmed.
班克斯和申克
Banks and Schenk...
某个流浪汉被三号线列车撞了你们走一趟
Some homeless guy got hit by the 3 train. You're up.
彼得森警官
Detective Peterson,
接2 2 1号线彼得森警官接2 2 1号线
pick up 221. Detective Peterson, 221.
这是你的车?
This is you
小队行动车
Beats the squad car.
班克斯警官在前往10 19途中
Detective Banks en route to that 1019.
目标在街北面还是南面?
Would that be north or south side of the street
北面 收到
Northbound. Copy that.
你在干什么
What are you doing
哦这是我家人
Oh, it's just family.
这是我的妻子艾玛这是我儿子查理
This is my wife, Emma, this is my son, Charlie.
很可爱享受当下吧
They're cute. Enjoy it while it lasts.
当下?
"While it lasts"
没有比一名新警察的妻子更开心的人了
Nothing happier than the wife of a new detective,
也没有比十年后的
and nothing more angry
这些婊子更加暴躁的人
than that same bitch 10 years later.
她们暴躁也许这是因为你叫她们婊子
Maybe it's 'cause you call them bitches.
我有一半意大利血统相信我
I'm halfItalian, trust me.
女人可不喜欢你叫她们婊子
Women do not like it when you call them bitches...
你在教我关于女人的事情吗
What are you telling me about women,
小年轻可去你的
young motherfucker  Shit.
我只是跟你说没有跟别的女人说
I just said it to you, I didn't say it to a woman.
我可没有当着她们的面这么叫我可没这么傻
I don't say it to their face. It's not like I'm Too Short.
我们刚认识但是你就已经对我火力全开了真是谢谢你
We just met, but, you know, you're firing already, and I appreciate it.
我的意思是你懂的
I mean, all I'm saying is, you know,
大多数犯罪发生在周末或者假期
most crime happens on weekends, holidays,
所以嫁给警察的人
so you would think anybody married to a cop
最明白这一点
would understand this.
但是不是的
But no.
有一天你的妻子会因为
One day, your wife will be angry
你不能参加她姐妹的生日晚宴而生气
'cause you couldn't go to her sister's birthday dinner.
你可以陪你的女人过六百个周二
You can give a woman 600 Tuesdays.
但是这一切都不比在一起过三个周六的夜晚
It ain't worth three Saturday nights.
所以我猜你已经离婚了
So, uh... I'm guessing you're divorced.
还没我正在离婚
Divorced, no, not yet. I'm going through a divorce.
这更加糟糕跟化疗似的
That's even worse. It's kind of like chemo.
不好意思
Shit. Sorry.
什么不好意思我们是警察这就是我们选择的生活
Sorry for what  We're cops. This is the life we choose.
最高的离婚率最高的自杀率
Highest divorce rate, highest suicide rate.
最高的家暴率
Highest rate of domestic violence.
在你决定当一名警察的时候
Yo, when you decided to become a cop,
你就已经差不多能猜到
you pretty much assured yourself
自己以后将会孤独地死去
you were gonna die alone.
我和我的妻子我们正在做相关的咨询
My wife and I, we're doing this counseling.
她正在和我尝试着沟通
She's got me, uh, working on, like, communication.
咨询?哦真好
Counseling  Yeah, that's nice.
我的妻子和咨询顾问上床了
Yeah, my wife fucked the counselor.
靠真的吗?
Fuck, really
是的天啊
Yeah.  Jesus.
女人也会出轨
Women cheat, too.
这很伤心天啊这真的让我伤心
It hurts. God damn it, it hurts.
女人也会出轨但是事情是这样的
Women cheat, too, but here's what happens.
女人在白天出轨
Women cheat in the daytime.
而白天你忙得一团糟
You can get away with a lot of shit in the daytime.
事实就是这样女人就可以
That's right. You can ride
在黄昏之前同很多男人上床 嗯
a lot of dick before dusk.  Mmmhmm.
靠伙计我才意识到她没有报什么普拉提课
Shit, man, I just found out Pilates doesn't even exist.
等会真的吗?
Wait, seriously
艾玛非常喜欢做普拉提
Emma loves Pilates.
是的她肯定很喜欢
I'm sure she does. I'm sure she does.
但是不要担心
But don't worry about it.
你会没事的你们的婚姻将会永恒
You're gonna be fine. You gonna be married forever.
现场如何
What do we got
自己看
See for yourself.
小心点
Watch yourself.
啊
Ah!
你要是想吐别吐在证物上就行
If you're gonna throw up, don't do it on the evidence.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me
我从十二岁开始做梦都在想当警察侦查现场
I've been dreaming about this since I was 12 years old.
啊
Ugh.
你在地铁上看太多电视剧了么
You see a lot of TV sets on the subway
你把这儿事都做完
You get everything down here.
该死天呐
Damn. Wow.
啊
Ugh.
这个乞丐很难确定身份
This bum's gonna be tough to ID.
我可不敢确定这是个乞丐
I'm not too sure this is a bum.
我不知道很多流浪汉试图闯到这边来
I don't know a lot of bums trying to get their steps in.
不管这是谁反正结婚了
Whoever this is, is married...
还戴着个 Fitbit手环
and wears a Fitbit.
这是刚刚到的包裹
This package just came in.
给我的? 对
For me Yeah.
什么东西
What is that
“播放我”
"Play me."
好吧哇哇你要千啥
Okay.  Whoa, whoa. What are you doing
我可不想搞坏我自己的电脑
Don't want to fuck up my computer.
你好班克斯警探
Hello, Detective Banks.
我是来帮你们改造警察局的
I'm here to help reform the Metro Police,
让你们这些人想起曾经对这座城市的居民许下的誓言
to remind them of their oath to the people of this city.
你们局里的一个警官拒绝接受我的改造
One officer from your station refused to be reformed.
而他不会是最后一个参与我游戏的人
He will not be the last to play my game.
如果那个旋涡是我想到的那个
If that spiral is what I think it is...
竖锯?
Jigsaw
等等我觉得竖锯已经死了吧
Wait, I thought the Jigsaw killer was dead
是啊 但如果这是另一个模仿犯
Yeah, but if it's another copycat...
那可就糟透了
It's gonna be a shit show.
这个建筑我认识
I recognize that building.
是法院
It's the courthouse.
我们去核查一下
Let's check it out.
你们怎么在这
What are you guys doing here
我们觉得你们可能需要些帮助
Well, we thought you boys might need some backup.
去你的吧费奇关你屁事
Fuck you, Fitch, it's not your case.
嘿 泽克
Yo, Zeke.
来看看我们找到了什么
What do we got here
那他妈是什么东西
What the fuck is that
该死的那是个舌头吗
Is that a fucking tongue
操
Fucking shit.
4 5 3谁是4 5 3号
453... Who's 453
集合
Circle up
好了以下是已知信息
Okay, here's what we know.
根据牙医记录确认了是保斯
Dental records confirm it's Boz.
很遗憾伙计们
Sorry, guys.
但是听着我们得抓住干下这事儿的混蛋
But, look, we got to catch the son of a bitch that did this.
列车员说他没看到什么东西
Train conductor says he didn't see much.
据说他看见保斯从天上掉下来
Says he saw Boz hanging in the air
砸到了挡风玻璃上
right before he hit the windshield.
他说看见保斯嘴巴里在大出血
Says he thinks he saw Boz bleeding from the mouth badly.
这包裹是送货服务送来的
The package was sent from a delivery service
然后我们在安格林街上的栅栏里捡到了它
that picked it up on a stoop on Anglin Drive.
那么关于那个漩涡图案呢
What about the spirals
嘿 警长这很明显是个竖锯的模仿犯啊
Hey, Cap, obviously it's a Jigsaw copycat,
这才是我们应该关注的点
so that's where we got to concentrate our focus.
当然了费奇但我想要你继续寻找确凿证据
Sure, Fitch, but I want you to stick with hard evidence.
克劳斯与联调局的人联系看看他们有什么发现
Kraus, contact the Feds, get anything they got.
文件旧视频任何东西
Files, old videos, anything.
我们有街道监控吗
Do we have street images
我们正在处理数字取证可以
We're working on it, but Digital Forensics was
帮助绘制出 Fitbit手环上保斯的行动路线
able to map Boz's movement off the Fitbit.
在放烟花的时候被实时追踪到的
Last place it was registered was Stuart's Point,
最后一个地点是斯图亚茨角
timestamped during the fireworks.
得有人给卡拉打电话那是他的妻子得让她知道发生了什么
Someone needs to call Kara, his wife, let her know.
嗯我已经跟她说过了
Yeah, I already called her.
你给卡拉打了电话
You called Kara
是啊
Yeah.
你认识卡拉 不
Do you know Kara   No.
你真的跟她说话了吗或者你是给她发的消息
Did you actually talk to her, or did you text her
让我猜猜你发了个表情
Let me guess, you sent an emoji.
他们有死掉的丈夫的表情吗
Do they have a dead husband emoji
我跟她说话了你个混蛋
I talked to her, asshole.
嘿 我们得在消息被走漏给记者前通知到她
Hey. We had to notify her before it leaked to the press.
好了让奥布莱恩来…
Okay, O'Brien's got point...
奥布莱恩?
O'Brien
这本该是我案子
This is mine.
我和卢克是最先到现场的
Me and the rook were first on scene.
班克斯
Banks...
抱歉这难道不是规定吗
I'm sorry, isn't this protocol
现在你又是团队的一员啦泽克
Now you're part of the team again, Zeke
去死吧你
Fuck you.
你才去你妈的死
No, fuck you.
拜托泽克
Come on, Zeke.
当所有你们这些混蛋对我那么糟糕
When all you motherfuckers were treating me like shit,
在背后中伤我
shooting me in my fucking back,
只有保斯拿我当朋友
Boz was my friend
是保斯陪我的孩子玩耍
Boz played with my kid.
陪我的孩子参与游戏活动
We went to fucking games.
我该死你们他妈的才该死
Fuck me  No, fuck you.
该死的混蛋
Fucking assholes...
泽克泽克他妈的站住
Zeke  Zeke, fucking stop
进来谈现在
In here  Now
拉上拉链滚出去
Zip up  Get out.
好的警长
Okay, Captain.
天啊老兄洗洗手吧
Damn, nigga, wash your hands.
我知道你为什么想要主理这个案子
I get why you want this.
保斯也是我的朋友但你不能单独行动
Boz was my friend, too, but you can't do this alone.
我需要整个局里齐心协力一起侦破这个案件
I need the whole department on this, working together.
我没有试图单独行动好吗
I'm not trying to do this alone, okay
保斯是我的家人老大你得让我领头
Boz is my family, man. You gotta let me take lead.
你得让我亲自抓住这个该死的混蛋
You gotta let me catch this motherfucker.
好了各位我们计划有变
All right, guys, we got a change of plans.
班克斯现在开始是领队
Banks is taking lead.
听好了
Listen up.
我知道你们有人觉得我是小人
I know some of you guys think I'm a rat.
有人觉得我是告密者
Some of you think I'm a snitch.
还有人在气我跟你妈滚了床单
Some of you are mad I fucked your mother.
最后有人见到保斯
Boz was last seen
是在六月四号斯图亚茨角的巡游
at the July 4th parade at Stuart's Point...
所以那里应该有很多监控录像
...so there should be plenty of surveillance footage,
所以去检查你们社交媒体上的热门标签发的ins
so check your hashtags, Instagram...
嘿
Hey
我们这现在死了个警察各位有人残忍地杀害了他
Now, we got a dead cop here, guys, who was brutally killed.
他从天上掉下来舌头还被拔走了
A fallen brother whose tongue was ripped out.
我们需要集中注意力解决这件事
We need to focus on the case and solve this.
所以把录像找来给班克斯探员
So get the footage to Detective Banks
把你们自己的破事先放一边
and put your personal shit aside.
奥布莱恩你怎么说
O'Brien, you good
我会服从命令警长
No problem here, Captain.
很好
Good.
我们出发吧
Let's go.
喂我们去哪
Yo, where we going
为了以示尊重穿上制服
Pay our respects. Put on a suit.
泽克
Zeke...
卡拉
Kara...
会没事的
It's okay.
不管是谁干的我一定会找到他们
Whoever did this, I'm gonna find them.
我不明白这究竟是怎么发生的
I don't understand... How did it happen
卡拉你妈妈来电话了
Kara, your mother's on the phone.
好好的
Yeah, okay.
泽克
Zeke.
丽莎
Lisa.
你还好吗我我给你发了信息
You okay  I, uh... I texted you.
嗯我收到了
Yeah, I got it.
布莱恩在这吗
Is Brian here
没在我姐姐那儿呢
No, my sister's watching him.
你姐姐所以朗达都可以见我儿子而我不能
Your sister... So, Rhonda gets to see my son, but I don't
我们确定要在这里讨论这个吗
Are we really gonna do this here
不 不是今天
No. Not today.
嘿 我是威廉 停
Hey, I'm William.  Stop.
泽克的搭档嗯
Zeke's partner, yup...
我在外面等着我在外面等着
I'll wait outside. I'll wait outside.
詹米还在邻居家
KARA: Jamie's at the neighbor's.
我不知道我该怎么告诉他他爸爸发生了什么事
I don't know how I'm supposed to tell him what happened to his dad.
我不敢想象你们当下要怎么熬过去
I can't imagine what you're going through right now.
我知道现在并不是个好时候
I know this is a bad time,
但我还是得问你几个问题
but I got to ask you a couple of questions.
在过去的几周
In the last few weeks,
你有关注到什么不寻常的事吗
did you notice anything unusual
我的意思是保斯有说过什么或是表现得压力很大
I mean, did Boz say anything, or act stressed out
他是个警察泽克
He was a cop, Zeke.
所以并没有什么不寻常的事
So nothing out of the ordinary
没有
No.
倒是有一件事有一辆黑色的SUV
There was one thing, there was a black SUV
上周在外边停了一整晚
parked outside one night last week.
有看到是什么牌子的车吗
You get a make
路虎凯迪拉克林肯?我不知道
Range Rover, Escalade, Lincoln   I don't know.
我跟保斯说了这件事然后他出去了
I told Boz about it and he went out,
他走过去然后我不知道
and he walked up, and, I don't know,
接下来他冲里面的人喊叫
the next thing I know, he was yelling at somebody inside.
知道他们说了什么吗
Any idea what they were yelling about
你有没有听到什么
Did you hear anything
没有如果我再见到我会记下车牌号
No. If I see it again, I'll get a license plate.
如果你不介意的话你能把他的设备之类的都给我吗
If you don't mind, could you get me his devices
我需要查看他的iPad笔记本电脑
I need to look at his iPad, laptop.
好的 谢谢卡拉
Yeah.  Thanks, Kara.
好啦我得走了孩子们注意安全
Nice... I gotta go, guys. All right, be safe.
泽克
Zeke.
他知道你是个好警察
He knew you were a good cop.
你一定要找到是谁干的
You find out who did this.
你拿枪口对着你老子
You pull a gun on your old man
你他妈是疯了吗∥
You out of your fucking mind
我差点就杀了你了
I could have killed you.
你在说些什么我有枪
What are you talking about  I got the gun.
我差点就把你杀了
I could have killed you.
你是怎么进来的
How'd you get in here
你忘了谁才是房东了吗
Did you forget who the landlord is
好吧但这并代表你有权利
Yeah, but that doesn't give you the right
想什么时候进来就什么时候进来
to just walk in here anytime you want.
租客也是有权利的
Renters got rights.
你要是开始付房租你就能得到一些权利
You start paying some rent, you can get some rights.
我听说了保斯的事儿了你怎么样
Heard about Boz. You all right
不太好老爸我我感觉一塌糊涂
No, Dad, I'm... I'm fucked up.
非常遗憾我知道你们关系很要好
Sorry to hear that. I know how close you were.
竖锯模仿犯这可有点儿难度
Jigsaw copycat.That could be difficult.
- 你在说什么 - 什么也没说
- What are you saying  - Nothing.
就只是你懂的做领头的
Just, you know, being lead detective,
总是有很多责任
a lot of responsibility.
你有意见吗
You got a problem with that
或者你只是害怕我会让你难堪
Or are you just scared I'm gonna embarrass you
看见了吗这就是问题所在
See  That right there.
这跟你没有关系
This ain't about you.
你总是觉得有些破事儿和你有关
You always making shit about you.
然而正是这些破事儿毁掉了你的职业生涯
That's the shit that ruined your career
以及你的婚姻
and your marriage.
所以你现在是给我提来自父亲的建议咯
So, now you're giving fatherly advice
你在说些什么威廉
What you talkin' 'bout, Willis
爸我们住在同一栋楼
Dad. We live in the same building.
我前几天在外边儿见到你
I saw you out front the other day,
你跟我点了个头就像我们只是商场里两个素不相识的黑人
you nodded at me like we were the only two black guys in the mall.
我们过去的一年都没在一起吃过一顿饭
We haven't had a meal together in over a year.
都没在一起吃过饭
Haven't had a meal
怎么你饿了小鬼
What  Are you hungry, nigga
你想他妈的吃点啥
You want to go get a fucking slice
让我告诉你
Let me tell you something.
我爸去工作然后回家就是这样
My father went to work, came home. That was it.
好吧我马上离开这里儿子
All right, I'm gonna get out of here, son.
我接下来去卡拉家表达我的敬意
I'm gonna go to Kara's, pay my respects.
一切都会好起来的
You're gonna be all right.
今晚过来我定了餐我们一起顺一遍这个案子
Come over tonight, I'll order some food, we'll go over the case.
只是因为你爹曾经是个警长 那个该死的马库斯·班克斯…
Just because your dad was Chief fucking Marcus Banks...
别把我爸扯进来十二年前
Stop making this about my father. Twelve years ago,
我检举了一个黑警察
I turned in a dirty cop.
彼得彼得
Pete  Pete
怎么了发生什么了
What happened  What happened
他拿枪指着我
He pulled a gun on me.
证人拿枪指着你吗
The witness pulled a gun on you
因为警队里我他妈没有人能信任
Because there's nobody on the force I can fucking trust
我已经盯着这玩意儿看了五个小时了
I've been staring at this shit for five hours.
毛片我都没看过这么久
I don't even look at porn that long.
好的我这完成了下一个是谁
Okay, I'm out. What's next
嗯不如你去查一查数字取证
Well, why don't you check with Digital Forensics
看看保斯手机通讯录里有没有谁有辆黑色SUV的
and see if anybody in Boz's phone log has a black SUV
我手机没电了你有充电器吗
My phone is dead, you got a charger
你手机没电了你谁啊小姑娘么
Your phone's dead, what are you, a little girl
得了你手机借我
Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
行
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
别拿去看《暮光之城》之类把我手机耗没电了
Don't drain my battery watching Twilight.
很高兴看到你加入我们
Glad to see you joined us.
你认为这个和约翰·克雷默(老竖锯)有关吗
You think this is linked to John Kramer
我已经把部分照片发给联邦调查局了让我们到时候看看结果
I sent some pictures to the Feds, we'll see what happens.
监控那里有线索吗
How are we doing on surveillance
告诉我咱们城市花两千万造的监控系统总发现了点什么吧
Please tell me the $20 million the city spent on cameras got us something
德鲁里
Drury
呃从这到这儿的街角监控
Yeah...Street cameras from here to here
都检查过了
have already been scrubbed through.
面部识别系统也没有任何发现
Facial recognition came up with nothing.
在这个角落有两个摄像头坏了
There were two cameras broken on this corner.
费奇和克劳斯已经去调查了
Fitch and Kraus are there now to canvas it.
不关门了打样了
No. Closed. Closed.
保斯在这
There's Boz.
他追着那人是谁
Who's that he's chasing
我认识那家伙
I know that guy.
本尼怀特他是个骗子
Benny Wrights. He's a hustler.
真正的变态
Serious tweaker.
藏在12区一个烧毁的面包厂里
Flops in a burntout bread factory down on 12th.
跟一个毒贩打交道街头名施彼斯
Deals with a pusher, street name Speez.
我们该告诉泽克吗 去他的
Should we tell Zeke   Fuck him.
我来检查大楼你追踪施彼斯
I'll take the building, you track down Speez.
老板让我看看你那里的枪
Hey, boss, let me see that gun over there.
左边那把对对给我看看
The one on the left. Yeah, yeah, come on, come on.
代表国民护卫队
On behalf of the Metro Police,
我感谢你的慷慨
I want to thank you for your generosity.
我还有事要做我先走了
I got shit to do. I'm out.
他什么情况
What's his deal
他就是一坨屎
He's a crooked piece of shit.
今天就到此为止吧 你确定吗
Let's just call it a night.   You sure
是回家吧
Yeah. Go home.
回家照顾你老婆看看你孩子
Go see your wife, go see your kid.
你儿子叫什么来着
What's your boy's name
查理查理
Charlie.  Charlie.
行那我回去把他哄睡着就马上回来
All right, I'll put him down and come right back.
不 不 不我马上也走了
No, no, no, I'm not going to be here.
晚上要和我爸吃饭梳理一下案子
Meeting my dad for dinner, gonna go over the case.
好吧
Okay.
嗨威廉
Hey, William.
怎么了
Yeah
今天干得不错
Good work today.
谢了兄弟
Thanks, man.
明天见 嗯
See you tomorrow.  Yeah.
本尼
Benny
醒醒本尼
Wake up, Benny.
起来干活了兄弟
Rise and shine, my man.
本尼该起了
Benny, come on. Get up.
得了本尼起来
Come on, Benny, get up.
你还好吗
You all right
哦操
Fuck me.
这里是黛博拉克劳斯我不在请给我留言
This is Deborah Kraus, leave me a message.
克劳斯给我回电
Kraus, call me.
这里是警官奥布莱恩
This is officer O'Brien
给我留言我会给你回电
leave a message and I'll get back to you.
救命救救我
Help  Help me
你好费奇警探
Hello, Detective Fitch.
我想和你玩个游戏
I want to play a game.
你好泽克 威廉
Hey, Zeke.  William.
你在干嘛呢
What are you doing up
我告诉过你今晚好好休息
I told you to take the rest of the night off.
呃没事查理睡着了
Uh, it's fine, Charlie's sleeping.
结果又醒了
Was sleeping.
我只是在等艾玛回家她今晚和闺蜜聚会去了
Just waiting for Emma to get home, she's having a girl's night.
闺蜜之夜哦行吧
Girl's night out. Okay.
你讲话当心一点
You better be careful with that,
说不定是乱搞之夜
might be a dick night out.
你自己的婚姻面临破裂
Just because you're getting a divorce,
可不代表别人的婚姻都会终结
it doesn't mean that everyone else's marriages have to end, too.
听起来你这会挺忙
Sounds like you got your hands full.
要我待会再打给你吗
You want to call me back
不没事
Nah, it's okay,
我在给孩子做入睡训练简直是噩梦
we're sleeptraining. It's a fucking nightmare.
听着兄弟呃我知道你和保斯走得近
Look, man, um... I know you and Boz were close,
我不知道该怎么跟你讲
I don't know how to tell you this.
你有事想说说吧威廉
You got something to say, William, say it.
嗯我按你的要求去调查了公共记录
Well, I'm looking through all the Metro records like you asked,
发现保斯被指控作伪证
and Boz was accused of lying on the stand more than anybody...
长期滥用职权
by like a wide fucking margin.
老天
Jesus.
法院
The courthouse...
这就是舌头被放在法院大楼的原因
That's why the tongue was at the courthouse.
有事儿吗
Can I help you
你是马库斯·班克斯吗
Are you Marcus Banks
不我是他儿子 行这是泰罗尼的外卖
No, I'm his son.  Well, Terroni delivery.
哦行
Oh, okay.
爸
Dad
老爹你外卖在这
Pop, got your food.
他妈的
Motherfucker
你他妈怎么不先给我打电话
How the fuck could you not call me first
我打了你没接
I tried, but you didn't answer.
行那你怎么不等到我给你回电话
Well, why didn't you wait for me to fucking call you back
因为你会劝阻我
'Cause you would have talked me out of it.
我说了实话
I told the truth.
滚出我的视线泽克
Get the fuck out of my face, Zeke.
能让我们单独谈吗
Can we get the room
该死的
God damn it.
我早就知道不该让他当警察
I knew I should have never let him become a cop.
这种破事传起来很快
This shit's gonna go sideways fast.
他检举了一个黑警察彼得是个小人
He turned in a dirty cop. Pete was a scumbag.
媒体会把他形容成英雄
Press will make him out to be a hero.
那其他警察呢
And what about the other cops
你觉得他们也会叫他英雄吗
You think they're gonna call him a hero, too
他做了正确的事情
He did the right thing.
你知道我得做多少内部损耗控制的工作吗
You know how much internal damage control I have to do
我们能处理好的
We'll handle it.
我们一直都是如此不是吗
We always do, huh
班克斯警长我是 WF Action新闻社的
Chief Banks, WF Action News here.
你在吗
Are you in
哦抱歉但我觉得你的脸
Oh, I'm sorry, but I think your face
擅自侵入了我的地盘
was trespassing on my property.
我能帮到你什么吗
Is there something I can help you with
没
No.
行麻烦你滚吧
All right. Fuck you very much.
给警探泽克·班克斯的
For Detective Zeke Banks.
班克斯给你的
Banks, incoming.
放到我桌上现在
On my desk. Right now.
一个快递员送来的
A courier brought it.
我们正扣下他问话
We're holding him for questioning.
你好警探班克斯
Hello, Detective Banks.
救赎已经提供但却遭到拒绝
Salvation was offered, but it was declined.
这个混蛋当自己是竖锯
This fucker thinks he's Jigsaw.
这把都有玩偶了
Even got a doll this time.
我与警察局有些分歧争执
I have a bone to pick with the police department,
如果你们打算指手画脚
and if you're going to point fingers...
12号街的桥下我认识这个地方
12th Street Bridge. I know that place.
你们最好该从自身开始
...you should start by pointing them at yourselves.
老天那有两个街区远
Geez, that's two blocks away.
直到你们坦白一切前还有很多人会牺牲
Until you come clean, many more will die.
待在后面
Stay back.
保持警惕
Stay sharp.
喔等等各位
Whoa, hold it there, guys.
真是个变态啊兄弟
What a sick fuck, man.
什么情况
What the fuck
哦不
Oh, no...
老天啊
God almighty.
九八二
982.
是费奇
It's Fitch.
这里是警探班克斯
This is Detective Banks
请求支援
requesting backup.
我在德克街请求支援
I'm on Decker Street. Request backup
去他的现在立刻
Fuck him. In pursuit,
请求支援
requesting backup
啊可恶我操
Ah, fuck   Fuck me.
你会没事的保持清醒
You're going to be okay, stay with me.
你没事你会好的
You're good, you're gonna be okay.
你会没事的
You're gonna be just fine.
泽克先生拜托拜托
Zeke   Sir  Please, please
让我们做我们的工作拜托
Let us do our job, come on.
拜托让我们完成我们的工作我们走我们走
Come on, let us do our jobs, let's go. Let's go.
你们都他妈上哪去了啊
Where the fuck were all of you, huh
我儿子八分钟里叫了三次增援
My son called for backup three times in eight minutes
你们他妈的一个都不来
and none of you motherfuckers could get here
没人一个也没有
Nobody  Nothing
行好我接下来打算这么办
Crickets. All right, this is what I'm going to do.
我马上打电话给调遣部
I'm going to call Dispatch
找出谁是距离最近的那个
and find out who was closest available,
等我找出是谁我会拿着这把枪
and when I do, I'm going to take this gun
射那个混蛋
and shoot that motherfucker.
听懂了吗
We clear
费奇是你吗
Fitch, it was you
你又搞我儿子是吧
You fucking with my son again
操你妈狗娘养的
God damn you, son of a bitch
放开我
Get off me
你完了混蛋你听见没
You're done, motherfucker, you hear me
你他妈完了
You're fucking done
别再让我看见你
Don't let me see your face again.
行了打给克劳斯
All right, call Kraus,
找到费奇的最后地点在哪
find out Fitch's last location.
你好费奇警探
Hello, Detective Fitch.
我想和你玩个游戏
I want to play a game.
审判之潮正在上升
The tide of justice is rising around you.
在90秒内水位会上涨到
In 90 seconds, the water will rise
铜导线的位置
to the height of the copper wires,
如果你仍在水池里
and if you are still in the tank,
你会被施以电刑
you will be electrocuted.
除非你做出牺牲以示忏悔
Unless you make the sacrifice that will cleanse you.
老天 哦 老天
FITCH: God... Oh, God...
你谋杀了一个男人仅因为他辱骂了你
You murdered a man because he insulted you.
把你的手放到
Put your hands
我看得见的位置混球
where I can see them, motherfucker.
我说把你的手放到我看得见的地方先生
I said put your hands where I can see them, sir.
你的手指扣动了扳机
Your finger pulled the trigger
这不会再发生了
and that cannot happen again.
存活很简单但它需要代价
Survival is simple, but it comes with a sacrifice.
咬下你嘴里的装置
Bite down on the device in your mouth,
它会启动发动机
which will start the motor
把你的手指撕掉
that will rip your fingers away...
还你自由
...leaving you free
逃回你的生活中
to escape with your life.
但如果你不迅速做出选择
But if you don't act quickly,
等待你的结局就在这个浴缸里
all that awaits you is this watery tomb.
生存还是毁灭请做出选择
Live or die, make your choice.
克劳斯我们找到手指的那座桥有什么与众不同吗
Hey, Kraus, anything special about the bridge where we found the fingers
对啊为什么选那座桥啊
Yeah, why that bridge
他就是在那座桥上枪杀吉米林肯的
It was where he shot that kid, Jimmy Lincoln.
那你们是怎么找到这儿的
Then how did you guys find out about this place
这个本尼怀特
This guy, Benny Wrights,
就是保斯七月四号见到的最后一个人
who Boz was last seen with on July 4th.
你怎么知道保斯最后见的谁
How do you know who Boz was last seen with
我们从斯图亚茨角的一家当铺了解到的
We took it off a pawn shop feed in Stuart Point.
你没跟我说过
And you didn't tell me.
到底谁干的
Who the fuck did this
估计是个伸张正义的城市警察吧
Somebody who has it out for the Metro PD.
或者是为了费奇
Or maybe just for Fitch.
德鲁里你有什么话就直说吧
You trying to say something, Drury
你知道我想说什么吗
You know what I'm saying.
我怀疑就是你在给费奇打掩护
I doubt you'll be shedding tears for Fitch.
好了别这样泽克
All right, come on. Come on, Zeke.
狗娘养的
Fucking asshole.
好了好了别理他
Okay, ignore him.
你手头有什么线索了吗
Did you get anything
现在我手头有个名字本尼怀特这是保斯最后见的人
Got a name. Benny Wrights. Last guy Boz was seen with.
好吧我们得快点找到他时间不多了
Okay, find him, and you got hours, not days.
本尼就是在这里搞到毒品的
And this is where Benny gets his meth.
你知道那是什么吗
You know what that is
你是在测试我吗
Is this a test
只是问个问题而已呃卖毒品的地方
Just asking you a question.  Uh, it's a meth house.
你把钱放在桶里他们就把货给你
You put the money in the bucket, the meth comes down.
看来你看过《火线》
Oh, somebody watched The Wire.
这简直和《万恶城市》里一模一样
This is some New Jack City shit. Goddamn.
我们不需要搜查令吗
Don't we need a warrant for this
说什么傻话呢
What you talking about
泽克
Zeke...
嘿 嘿 嘿 好兄弟
Hey, my man, my man.
给点货给我和我马子吧
Just trying to get a five, me and my lady
今天我俩周年纪念我们想庆祝一下
It's our anniversary, we're trying to celebrate,
只有这个才够劲儿
trying to do something special.
给点吧 求你了 我把这个平板电脑给你
Can I get a five  How about this iPad
这里面啥都有
It's got everything on it.
里面有 Passcodes, Netflix还有Hulu视频
I got passcodes, I got Netflix, Hulu,
你还可以直接在上面点餐你看吃的可多了
uh, Uber Eats, Postmates. Lots of food, lots of food.
我看看
Let me see that...
嘿 快滚吧
Yo, man, get the fuck out of here.
我看起来饿的不行了吗
Do I look fucking hungry to you
平板里啥都有但是这个桶装不下
Yo, yo, it got everything. It don't fit, though.
你下来一下可以吗
Why don't you come down
快滚吧
Get the fuck out of here
等你有钱的时候再来吧
Come back when you get some money
好吧好吧我需要钱啊
Okay, okay. I need money, I need money.
不 不 不等一下
No, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait
我还有点钱
I got some, I got some money.
等一下我找找
I got some money, hold up a second.
就等一下好吗
Hold up a second, all right
好了快把货送下来吧
All right, send it down, baby.
快点快点我们等不及了
Come on, come on, let's do this.
实在是等不及了
Can't wait
泽克你在干什么
Zeke, what the fuck
只有十秒钟快点
It's got 10 seconds, come on
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
这他妈是啥
What the fuck
闪一边一别挡道
Move   Get out of the way.
警察靠边靠边
Out of my way, out of my way  Police
条子
MAN: Fiveo
条子进来了一边儿去快点
Everybody, fiveo   Move, move, move  Come on
快穿过去
Go  Coming through.
该死的条子
MAN: Fucking cops, man.
哇呜哇呜
Whoa, whoa, whoa
该死把你的狗拴好
Shit  Get your dog
操他妈的 把你的狗牵好
MAN: Fuck you, man.  Get your fucking dog
这狗日的 嘿 别这么凶嘛
Now   Hey, be nice.
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
真他妈该死
Holy fucking shit.
发生怎么了
What the fuck's going on
滚回去跟你没关系
Back inside. Get back inside.
管好你自己
Hide your shit
来啊
Come on
操操
Fuck. Fuck
我的腿啊
My fucking leg
你为什么还要给我增加难度
Why do you make this shit so hard
要是我一不小心杀了你呢
What if I really wanted to get fucked up
你这狗娘养的
Motherfucker...
顾客就是上帝搞这么复杂干什么
You got to make it easy for the customer, skeeve
我的腿啊我的腿断啦
My fucking leg
这条腿已经没救了
That leg is fucked up.
哟哟哟哟
Yo, yo, yo, yo
来让我拍一张发朋友圈
Let me get a shot for the Gram.
你这个表情不错
Hold on for one second.
日你妈别动别动
DRUG DEALER: What the fuck... Hold on, hold on.
我的好兄弟
My man.
好了需要我艾特你吗
Here we go  You want me to tag you
艾特你大爷
Fuck... Fuck you.
要不要艾特你啊你这杂种我日你
Can I tag you, motherfucker   Fuck you...
你之前见过这个人吗
You see this man before
我一个字也不会告诉你
I ain't telling you shit
你不说我就只好问问你的断腿了
Why, 'cause you're worried about that bone sticking out your leg
来我来帮你消消毒
Why don't you let me sterilize it
不 不 不操
No... No... No  Fuck
停停停求你了是本尼
It's Benny  Stop, please
大家都认识那个该死的本尼怀特
Everybody knows that motherfucker Benny Wrights
他是我的客户之一
He's one of my best customers, man.
你最后一次见他是什么时候
When was the last time you saw him
我已经好几天没见过他了
I ain't seen the bitch in two days, man.
这条街上每个人都知道他吸毒
Word on the street is that motherfucker OD'd.
现在你成告密者了
Fuck this snitch.
操
Fuck
我们这是在浪费时间
Well, that was a waste of time.
本尼已经死了
Well, we know Benny's dead.
买毒品可不是小打小闹得花不少钱
Meth isn't the type of thing you take a break from.
而且你仔细看那个刑具没
Besides, you see that device
牙齿不好都戴不上去
That was not designed by anybody with rotten teeth.
你觉得这个像不像竖锯的风格
What do you think about this whole Jigsaw angle
你觉得这应该是竖锯的门徒之一吗
You think it's a, whatdoyoucallthem, one of those disciples
约翰·克雷默不是冲着警察来的
John Kramer didn't target cops.
他另有目的
Whoever did this has another motive.
应该是私人原因
Something personal.
他们应该不是受他人之命
And they're not following orders,
况且竖锯早就死了
especially the orders of a ghost.
或者根本没死
Ghost or not,
有人在幕后操纵着这一切
somebody's out there pulling all the strings.
你觉得之所以这些人给你寄来了盒子
You think this guy sent you the boxes
是因为你是这件案子的主要负责人吗
because you're the lead detective on the case,
有可能只是为了你
or because you're you
不知道
I don't know.
你有什么死对头吗警察除外
Well, you got any enemies  That aren't cops
我不知道为什么她就是不肯原谅我
I don't know why she won't give me another chance.
可能是因为你一喝多
I don't know, maybe it's because you beat her
就打她吧
when you drink too much.
你有想过吗
You ever think of that
你的爱实在是太沉重了这人是谁
That's some tough love. Who the hell is this guy
前警察他的同伴出卖了他
Excop. Partner snitched on him,
九年来他过得不容易
had to do nine years hard time.
警局也不管他了现在他只能来这儿
The system spit him out, now here he is.
嘿 彼得
Hey, Pete.
泽克
Zeke.
见到你真晦气
Last guy I expected to see here.
你来这醒酒的吗
You trying to get sober
我对酒不感冒
Alcohol's not my problem.
但是酒精和酒瓶可以杀人
The glass and the bottle can kill.
最近怎么样彼得
How you doing, Pete
18个月了我在教堂的地下室里滴酒未沾
Eighteen months sober, living in a church basement,
你问我怎么样
who could ask for anything more
这是谁
Who's this
申克警探我们一起查这案子
Detective Schenk. We're working a case together.
一起查案
PETE: Working together
可别让这家伙抓住你的小辫子
Don't let this guy catch you jaywalking,
保不准他让你直接身败名裂
or he'll stab you right in the fucking back.
别忘了彼得你自己把小辫子递我手里的
Don't forget, Pete, you gave me the knife.
是啊 是我
You're right, I did.
你确定是这名警官
And you witnessed this cop
把被害人从屋顶扔下去的
throw the victim off a rooftop
真的是亲眼所见吗
And you saw it, I mean, with your own eyes
你可以指认这名警官吗
And you can positively ID this cop
他已经在这个社区横行霸道太久了
He's had his foot on the neck of this community for way too long.
我们实在是受不了了
We can't have this.
我会当场指认他的邓利维警官
I'll testify, Officer Dunleavy. I'll do it.
彼得彼得发生什么事了
Pete  Pete  What happened  What happened
他刚刚拿枪指着我
He pulled a gun on me.
目击者拿枪指着你你认真的吗
The witness pulled a gun on you
我郁闷了很久但是我现在已经承担后果了
I was mad for a long time, but now I take responsibility.
我不该开枪的
I should have never pulled the trigger.
那家伙还有一大家子人等着他呢
The guy had a family.
当时我真是疯了
It was crazy back then, right
在这种环境下生活
We were working under Article 8.
我也是身不由己了
We were out of control.
面对犯罪的时候警察都有自己的判断
Cops were given their own discretion to crack down on crime.
你七月四号晚上九点半在哪里
Where were you July 4th at 9:30 p.m.
讲真你就是为这事而来的吗
Really  That's what you're here for
对我就是为这事儿来的
That's what I'm here for.
听着有几个家伙喝得醉醺醺的
Look, some guy came to a meeting drunk
一到这儿他们就胖揍了一个金主所以我就打回去了
and wanted to fight a sponsor, so I hit him.
打得他妈都不认得
Knocked him clean out.
然后警察来了而我现在还在缓刑期
Anyway, the cops came. I'm still on probation,
幸运的是奥布莱恩帮我摆平了
but lucky for me, it was O'Brien.
整件事情就过去了毕竟你知道
He let the whole thing slide because, you know...
他可是讲情分的
loyalty.
情分
Loyalty.
保重彼得
Take care, Pete.
上帝保佑你泽克
God loves you, Zeke.
会更保佑你
More than you.
我简直想不到那个家伙以前居然是警察
Can't believe that guy used to be a cop.
就是因为他枪杀了一个无辜的男孩所以你就背叛了他
He shot an innocent guy, but you turned on him
当警察还是要讲原则你得学着适应
There's a code, and you better learn how to follow it,
不然你这辈子都要担心有人会背后给你一刃
or you're going to spend the rest of your life watching your back.
听起来很有道理
Fair point.
或许咱俩搭档也不是什么坏事
Maybe it's a good thing they made us partners.
请留言
Leave a message.
老爸我现在在你公寓里
Yeah, Dad, I'm at your apartment.
我昨晚也来了
I was here last night.
看起来你一直没回家
It doesn't look like you've been home.
有空就回我一个电话
All right, give me a call.
你已接通威廉
You've gotten through to William,
请在滴声后留言
leave a message after the beep.
申克现在已经九点了
Schenk, it's 9:00 a.m.,
你这小子在哪快给我回电话
where the fuck are you  Give me a call.
告诉我发生了什么好吗
JEANNIE: Just tell me what happened, okay
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey  Hey  Hey
立刻把盒子放在地上
Put the box on the ground
轻轻放在地上举起手来快点
On the ground  Hands up  Hands up
放在地上举起手来举起手来
On the ground now  Hands up, hands up
不许动
Don't move
带他出去
Get him out of here.
带去拘留室
Take him to holding.
抱歉班克斯我没注意到他就溜进来了
I'm sorry, Banks, he blew right past me.
泽克别碰这个可能和之前的不一样
No way, Zeke, that one is not the same.
我在联系拆弹小组
I'm calling the bomb squad.
安吉你是我们的头
Angie, you're the head of the department.
我们已经有两名警员牺牲了没有时间了
We got two dead cops, there's no time.
所有人出去
Get everybody out.
出去出去大家都出去
Everybody out  Everybody out
走走走别待在这儿
Everybody, go
这他妈是人皮做的吗 呕
Is that fucking skin,  Ugh.
"班克斯警探我是不是把你惹毛了
"Am I getting under your skin, Detective Banks.
当你还在寻找尸体的下落时
Careful, while you're looking for more bodies to drop,
小心你项上人头"
"I'll take your head."
"项上人头...
"I'll take your head...
我是不是把你惹毛了"
Am I getting under your skin".
家庭照片这是我妻子艾玛
...family. This is my wife, Emma,
我儿子查理
this is my son, Charlie.
那他妈是什么东西
What the fuck is that
队长那下面有东西
Captain, there's something under here.
拜占庭颜料
Constantine Paints.
谢谢
Thanks, yeah.
跟我来吧
Follow me.
你是怎么知道这个地方的
O'BRIEN: How do you know about this place
泽克你是怎么知道这个地方的
Zeke, how do you know about this place
我爸以前总带我来这儿
My dad used to take me here.
各位注意脚下
Watch your step, gentlemen.
这儿以前不是卖肉的地方
It wasn't always a butcher shop.
以前是君土坦丁火车店
Used to be Constantine Trains.
就和玩具店差不多
Like a hobby shop.
我的天啊
O'BRIEN: Oh, my God.
有什么线索吗
Anything
我们正在分析录音带
FORENSICS: Well, we're analyzing the tape recording.
申克警探你好
Hello, Detective Schenk,
我想玩个游戏
I want to play a game.
你的成绩在警察学校名列前茅
You were head of your class at the Police Academy.
很明显他是在死后
He was obviously skinned...
被剥皮了
postmortem.
我想这么做是因为你父亲
Your dad's the reason I wanted to do this in the first place.
在他剥皮的时候
...the body was scored first...
先是把尸体划开将尸块切成条状
to remove the pieces in larger strips,
然后对胳膊以及颈部进行剥皮
arms, neck, as he ripped the skin...
也许他们让你我成为搭档是件好事
Maybe it's a good thing they made us partners.
尸体身上有搏斗留下的伤痕
Even the defensive wounds,
他显然试图反击过
he clearly tried to fight back,
这也解释了为什么他身上会有更深的伤口
which explains the deeper gashes.
队长请问一下
Captain, over here.
作案的是一位针对警察的连环杀手吗
Is it a serial killer targeting cops
受害者是警察队伍中的一员吗
Is the victim inside a policeman
无可奉告哈特局长今晚将发表声明
No comment. Commissioner Hart will make a statement tonight.
在我把这件事告诉他妻子之前
We got to try to keep his identity
咱们要尽量保护他的身份不向媒体公开
out of the press until I tell his wife.
班克斯警探我是不是把你惹毛了
"Am I getting under your skin, Detective Banks "
奥布莱恩
Hey, O'Brien.
怎么了头儿
Yeah, boss
看到泽克了吗
You seen Zeke
没有段时间没见着了
No, not for a while.
好我要去处理个案子
Okay, I'm heading down to Cold Case.
知道了队长
Copy that, Captain.
我需要调用所有可用的人员
I need all available units,
在第三大道和 Beaman大街交汇处有警员负伤
officer down 3rd and Beaman.
再次通报在第三大道和比曼大街交汇处
Please report, 3rd and Beaman.
我们有什么线索
What do we got
当时我正在贴罚单一个戴着猪头面具的家伙
I was writing a ticket and some guy in a pig's mask,
拿刀向我冲过来
he runs up on me with a knife.
所以他捅了一下你的胳膊然后就跑了
So, he stabs your arm and just takes off
我尽全力和他搏斗了然后他
I fought him off the best I could and he...
他就这么逃走了
He took off running.
他有什么要袭击你的理由吗
Is there any reason he would have to attack you
没有他就是想搅乱警察内部
No. He just wanted to mess with the cops.
当你还在寻找尸体的下落时
"Careful, while you're looking for more bodies to drop,
小心你项上人头
"I'll take your head."
安吉你现在是部门的领导了
Angie, you're the head of the department.
安吉
Angie...
操
Ah, fuck
安吉快接电话
Angie  Pick up
你好这里是安吉·加尔扎警官
Hey, you've reached Captain Angie Garza,
请在提示音后留言谢谢
leave a message at the tone. Thanks.
安吉马上回办公室那家伙来去找你了
Angie, get to the bullpen  He's coming for you.
操操操
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
该死
Shit
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey  Hey  Hey
喂 喂 喂
Hello  Hello  Shit
救命
help
Help
加尔扎队长你好
Hello, Captain Garza.
我想玩个游戏
I want to play a game.
你掩盖了你们部门的腐败
You have covered up corruption in your department,
从不为无辜的人伸张正义
never sticking your neck out for the innocent.
现在掩盖的下场将降临到你头上
Now, the coverup will be on you.
几秒钟后滚烫的蜡油
In a few seconds, boiling hot wax
将从你上方的管道流出
will be coming out of the pipe above you.
防止自己窒息而死的唯一方法就是
The only way to stop yourself from being suffocated
用你脖子下方的刀片
is to sever your spinal cord
切断自己的脊髓
with the blade beneath your neck,
那时蜡油将不再流下
which will stop the wax.
你无法逃避这个困境
You cannot walk away,
但可以选择苟且活命
but you can survive.
是生是死自己做选择
Live or die, make your choice.
操你妈
Fuck you
安吉安吉
Angie  Angie
给老子闪开
Get the fuck out of the way
为什么没人接电话
How come no one is answering the phone
一名警员遭受袭击这里他妈一片混乱
An officer was attacked, it's fucking chaos in here.
安吉安吉
Angie  Angie
安吉
Angie
泽克怎么了
Zeke, what's going on
他找到她了
He's got her
谁找到她了
Who's got her
那个杀人魔找到了安吉
The killer has Angie
你可能不知道那个杀手刚刚袭击了
I guess you didn't hear, the killer just
在第三大道和比曼大街交汇处的一名警察
attacked a cop at 3rd and Beaman.
那只是转移我们注意力的伎俩让我们不再盯着警局内部
That was just a diversion to get us out of the precinct.
她他妈在地下室
She's down in the fucking basement
你找到安吉了吗
Did you find Angie
在地下室她在地下室
In the basement, in the basement
安吉·加尔扎队长
Captain Angie Garza,
请给前台回电
call the front desk.
把门打开
Open it
给我快点
Hurry up
安吉
Angie
打开啊
Open it
好了
Okay.
操
Shit
没事的一切都会好起来的
It's okay, it's okay. It's gonna be fine.
哦我的天啊
Oh, my God.
没事的
It's okay.
不会有事的噢
It's okay... Oh...
全部封锁
Lock it down.
听懂我的意思了吗
You understand me
全部封锁确保没人能走出警察局
Lock it down, nobody gets out of this precinct.
我需要证物室
I need all the footage from the cameras
所有摄像头的监控画面
in the evidence room.
好的在这儿
Okay, here...
这里是电话打进来的时候
Here's when the call came in,
但是到你进来之前什么事情都没发生
but then there's nothing until you come in.
看这儿从13时11分跳到了13时24分是故障原因吗
You see right there, it jumps from 13:11 to 13:24. Glitch
应该不是故障原因你看
No, there's no glitch, because look,
在第一帧安全门是开着的
on the first frame, the safe door is open,
但是到了下一帧门就关上了
but on the next, it's shut.
有13分钟的录像遗失
There's 13 minutes missing.
这些录像
Access to this footage,
是通过电脑系统获取的吗
is that through the computer system
是的只需要一个警号和密码就可以获取
Yeah, we just need a badge number and a password.
我没法告诉你谁删了这段视频
I can't tell you who deleted the video,
但是我可以调取过去一天登录服务器的用户
but I can access who logged into the server over the past day.
奥布莱恩塔珀尼古拉奇
O'Brien, Tupper, Nicholazi...
等会儿谁的警徽号码是2 1 3
Wait... Who's badge number 213
彼得·邓利维我的老搭档
Pete Dunleavy, my old partner.
邓利维他应该没有权限的
Dunleavy  He shouldn't have access.
他都多久没上班了
How long's it been since he was even on the job
你要去哪儿
Where you going
去和彼得见个面
To pay Pete a visit.
泽克他不是唯一一个有权限的人
Zeke, he's not the only one
你父亲以前也有权限
Your father had access, too.
申克尸体的位置
Location of Schenk's body,
你说那是你父亲从小就带你去的地方
you said it was where your father took you as a kid.
你最后一次见到你父亲是什么时候
When was the last time you saw your father
今天早上 放屁
This morning.  Bullshit.
你个混蛋
Motherfucker
你他妈干什么泽克
What the fuck, Zeke
操你妈
Fuck you, man
操你妈 你他妈给我滚出去
Fuck you   Get the fuck out of here
让他滚出去操你妈你太偏执了
Get him out of here  Fuck you  You're too close
你对这件事太偏执了泽克
You're too close to this thing, Zeke.
彼得
Pete
请留言
Leave a message.
爸我已经给你打了三遍电话了
Dad, I've called you three times,
请你给我回个电话
please call me back
人们没完没了地提问题我懒得应付他们了
People are asking questions and I'm sick of making excuses.
你有什么想和我说的吗操
You got something to tell me  Fuck
你想玩游戏是吧你这个王八蛋
You wanna play games, motherfucker
好啊我玩
All right, I'll play.
你还好吗
You okay
嘿
Hey
救命
Help
彼得
Pete
彼得醒醒
Pete, wake up.
彼得
Pete
什么泽克
What  Zeke
操
Fuck.
快把我弄下来泽克
Get me the fuck down, Zeke.
快点
Come on
你侵入了电脑
You hacked the computer.
抹去了监控录像
You erased the surveillance footage.
我他妈不知道你在说什么泽克
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about, Zeke.
是你杀的安吉你说什么
Did you kill Angie   What
你杀的保斯
Did you kill Boz
你他妈到底在说什么
What the fuck are you talking about
是你杀的保斯
Did you kill Boz
保斯操
Boz  Fuck...
你他妈什么毛病泽克
What the fuck is with you, Zeke
赶紧他妈把我弄出去
Get me the fuck out of here
这是什么操蛋的复仇泽克
Is this some sick fucking revenge, Zeke
把我扔进大牢还不过瘾是吗
Putting me in jail isn't enough, huh
赶紧把我弄下来
Get me the fuck out of here
班克斯警探你好
Hello, Detective Banks.
我想玩个游戏
I want to play a game.
彼得·邓利维谋杀了一个无辜的人
When Peter Dunleavy murdered an innocent man,
于是你的事业就碎得像玻璃渣一样
your career was shattered like glass.
当正义最终得到伸张时
Can you stand on the sidelines
你还能袖手旁观吗
while justice is finally served
是找办法救他
There is a way to save him,
还是扔掉钥匙让他自生自灭
or you can keep him locked up and throw away the key.
决定权在你
The decision is yours.
扔掉钥匙这他妈在说啥
"Throw away the key," what the fuck
啊
Huh
快让我离开这个玩意儿
Get me the fuck out of this thing.
泽克
Zeke
我操
Oh, shit.
快点泽克
Come on, Zeke.
快点他妈放我下来泽克
Get me the fuck out of here, Zeke
操
Shit
泽克帮帮我
Zeke  Help me
泽克
Zeke
把我放下来求你了
Get me down, come on, man.
泽克
Zeke
或者你可以锁着他
...or you can keep him locked up
并且把钥匙扔掉
and throw away the key.
彼得
Pete
我来了彼得
I'm coming, Pete
我去
Shit.
他妈的打开了打开了
Fuck. I got you, I got you.
挺住啊彼得
Come on, Pete.
彼得
Pete
你这个不讲信用的家伙
You disloyal piece of shit.
从我们相遇的第一天起我一直都对你讲信用
I've been loyal to you since the first day we met.
十五年前
Fifteen years ago.
就在那天你搭档杀了我父亲
The day your partner killed my father.
那么查理
So, Charlie,
你看见这名警察把受害者扔下屋顶
you saw this cop throw the victim off a rooftop,
并且你能确认这名警察的身份对吗?
and you can positively ID this cop
我会作证的邓利维警官
I'll testify, Officer Dunleavy.
我会作证的
I'll do it.
彼得彼得发生什么了怎么了
Pete  Pete  What happened, what happened
他拿枪指着我
He pulled a gun on me.
目击者拿枪指着你?
The witness pulled a gun on you
嘘
Shh.
彼得杀了查理艾默森
Pete killed Charlie Emmerson.
什么?你以为我会用我的真名吗?
What  You thought I'd use my real name
你知道要进入这个部门
Do you have any idea how hard it was
还要被分配为你的搭档
to get placed in this department,
有多难吗?
to get assigned to be your partner
那你的家人呢?你的儿子呢?
What about your family, what about your son
这是我儿子查理
This is my son, Charlie.
我没有儿子
I don't have a son.
查理正在睡觉
Charlie's sleeping...
当时正在睡觉
...was sleeping.
本尼赖特诱导保斯维克进入地铁隧道之后
After Benny Wrights led Boz down the subway tunnels...
我把我爸的名字纹在了他胳膊上
I tattooed my dad's name on his arm.
我爸在哪儿?
Where is my father
你很快就会见到他了
You'll see him soon.
我爸到底在哪儿?
Where the fuck is my father
我甚至没叫他下来这里是你叫的
I didn't even ask him to come down here. You did.
把你电话借我闭嘴
Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
别把手机玩没电了
And don't drain my battery watching Twilight.
他在哪?
Where is he
难道你不想听听我的提议吗?
Don't you want to hear my offer
我有选择吗?
Do I have a choice
我想跟你合作
I want to be partners.
你选定了立场泽克反对黑警
You took a stand, Zeke, against a dirty cop,
而它给你带来了什么呢?
and what did it get you
生都要提防着身后独自工作
A lifetime of watching your back, working alone.
接听无家可归的流浪汉
Getting the call for every homeless bum
被发现死亡的电话
who turns up dead.
我的意思是让我们现实点吧这些混蛋
I mean, let's be real, some of these motherfuckers
有一些纯粹就是恶魔
are straight up evil.
费奇不支持你
Fitch not backing you up...
去他的
Fuck him.
他不会再重复那个错误了
He won't repeat that mistake.
还有保斯维克总是发了誓还撒谎
And Boz, always lying under oath...
但是你你不一样
But you, you're different.
你是片区里最好的警察
You're Metro's finest.
这就是我想和你合作的原因
That's why I want to team up with you on this.
你负责找出黑警我负责处理剩下的事
You find the dirty cops and I'll take care of the rest.
你想让我帮你杀警察?
You want me to help you kill cops
不是当然不是
No, fuck no.
我只针对坏的警察
Just the bad ones.
约翰·克雷默是对的关于漩涡
John Kramer was right, the spiral.
一个变化进化和进步的象征
A symbol of change, evolution, progress.
但是当你可以将它应用于整个系统时
But why limit that to an individual
为什么要将其限制在个人身上呢?
when you can apply it to a whole system
你因为做了对的事情而中枪
You got shot for doing the right thing.
但让我们面对现实吧这些警察?
But let's face it, these cops
他们是不会靠自己来整治腐败的
They're not going to clean up on their own.
但我们带条舌头到这来
But we take a tongue here,
带些尸骨到这他们就会赶来
a few bones there, they'll come around.
我们要修复一个破败的部门好吗?
We're going to fix a broken department. Okay
你和我
You and me.
好的
Okay.
好
让我们来做吧
Let's do it.
我想信任你真的
I want to trust you. I do.
我加入但你得放了我爸爸
I'm in. But my dad goes free.
等会儿
One second.
这里是911请说明你的紧急情况
911, please state your emergency.
你好呃我在马迪根路的那个
Hello, uh, I'm at the old soap factory
旧肥皂厂
on Madigan Lane.
这儿有个拿枪的疯子
There's a crazy guy with a gun,
他在到处开枪请快点赶来
he's firing it everywhere. Please hurry
那他妈的是哪一出?
What the fuck was that
你最好快点泽克特警就在路上
You better hurry, Zeke, SWAT's on the way.
听着我想相信你我真的想
Look, I want to believe you, I do.
我想信任你
I want to trust you.
拿着这个你会用到的
Take this, you'll need it.
人走吧
Come on.
我们去看看你爸爸
Let's go see your dad.
是时候进行你的最后一场测试了
It's time for your final test.
爸爸
Dad.
八泽克
Ezekiel.
妈的救他下来
Oh, shit  Get him down
靠
Oh, shit.
我来了爸爸
I got you, Dad.
泽克儿子帮帮我
Zeke. Help me, son.
别担心别担心
Don't worry, don't worry.
我不会让你死的我会救你下来的
I'm not going to let you die. I will get you down.
没问题等等就好
It's all right, just hold on.
现在向这混蛋开枪
Shoot this motherfucker right now.
救他下来现在救他下来
Get him down  Get him down now
我还以为我们是搭档
I thought we were partners.
你想对我开枪是吗?泽克
You going to shoot me, Zeke
就用你那一颗子弹吗?
With your one bullet
馊主意
Bad idea.
这么做会害死你爸爸
It kills your dad.
顺便说一下他朝我开了一枪
He took a shot at me, by the way.
没打中
Missed.
我浪费了四发
I wasted four.
说明你只剩下一发了泽克
That means you got one shot left, Zeke.
好吧警察来了我们有四分钟的时间
All right, cops are here. That gives us four minutes.
你知道人体内有1.5加仑的血液吗?泽克
Do you know there's 1.5 gallons of blood in the human body, Zeke
按照你那老父亲失血的速度
At the rate your old man is bleeding out,
那些容器只需要不到三分钟就会填满
in just three minutes, those jars will be full
然后你爸爸就会死掉
and your dad will be dead.
能让他获救的唯一物品
The only thing that can set him free
就是你朝那个靶子射出的子弹
is the bullet in your gun fired at that target.
不管怎样我都有万无一失的方法能离开这里
Either way, I've got a foolproof way out of here.
你不是竖锯
You're not Jigsaw.
那就是游戏
That's the game.
打死我你们就都输了
Shoot me and you both lose.
打靶子我们就都能赢
Shoot the target and we both win.
你想玩吗?
You want to play
我要死了泽克快动手吧
I'm dying, Zeke, end it now.
在这条走廊
In this corridor.
收到西南入口
Roger that. Southwest entrance.
穿过南门
Going through the south door.
这里没有发现继续前进
Nothing here. Keep moving.
我要你完全站在我这边
I need you all in.
邓利维毁了我们俩的生活
Dunleavy ruined both our lives
你还想着帮那混蛋吗?
and you tried to help that piece of shit
泽克彼得
Zeke   Pete
你没有通过测试
You failed that test.
现在我需要你选择你和谁真正在一起
Now I need you to choose who you're really with.
是那个破坏了正义的人
The man who corrupted the force,
还是那个试图挽救一切的人
or the one who's trying to save it.
你想告诉他吗?警长
You want to tell him, Chief
告诉我什么?
Tell me what
告诉他你在第八修正案掩护下做的恶心事
Tell him about all the fucking shit you did under Article 8.
他在说什么?
What's he talking about
时间在流逝 他在说什么?
Time's running out.  What's he talking about
人们在死去
Citizens were dying.
我们做了不得不做的事来清理街道
We did what we had to to clean up the streets.
那时候真是太疯狂了对吧?
PETE: It was crazy back then, right
我们在第八修正案下工作
We were working under Article 8,
我们失控了
we were out of control.
谋杀率大大下降了
Murder rate went way down.
那都是一派胡言
That's fucking bullshit.
人们再次感到安全
People felt safe again.
街道变干净了因为警察变脏了
The streets got cleaner because the cops got dirtier.
顺便说一下你爸爸目睹了全程
Your dad oversaw the whole thing, by the way.
无辜的人被枪杀全都是以正义的名义
Innocent people getting shot, all in the name of justice.
第八修正案是警察政策历史上
Article 8 was one of the most corrupt
最腐败的修正案之一
police policies in history,
猜猜你爸爸的得力助手是谁吧?
and guess who was your dad's righthand man
抱歉也许我应该说女助手自始至终都是
Sorry, or should I say woman, the whole time
我们会处理好的一直以来都能不是吗?
We'll handle it. We always do, huh
安吉?
Angie
安吉
是安吉
It was Angie.
我是想说这也没多意外
I mean, not a massive surprise.
你以为是她的好名声
You think it was her stellar reputation
让她在三十五岁的时候当上辖区警长的吗?拜托
that got her a precinct at age 35  Come on.
杀了这混蛋泽克就现在
Shoot this piece of shit, Ezekiel. Now.
是的没错因为那就是警察该做的事
Yeah, that's right, because that's what cops do.
先开枪后问话
Shoot first, ask questions later.
你目睹了我父亲的死亡而我想救你父亲
You watched my father die and I'm trying to save yours.
如果我们互相信任
If we're going to trust each other,
我需要你这么做
I need you to do this.
泽克
Ezekiel...
你过去总是做正确的事现在动手
You've always done the right thing, do it now.
这个混蛋在杀害警察
This piece of shit is killing cops.
你仍然需要做出决定
You still need to decide,
你可以朝我开枪或者
you can shoot me, or...
或者你可以救你爸爸
Or you can save your dad.
时间在流逝啊年轻人
Clock's ticking, man.
你得想快点了
Think fast.
特警要到了
Cavalry's coming.
但他们来不及救你那老父亲
But not in time to do any favors for your old man.
只有你能救他
Only you can do that.
爸爸?爸爸?
Dad  Dad
有人开枪了
Shots fired
泽克泽克
Zeke... Zeke.
会没事的
It's going to be okay.
他要跑了
He's getting away.
别让他跑了
Don't let him get away.
去快去
Go... Go
停下别进来
Stop. Don't come in.
不要进来
Don't come in.
噢天呐
Oh, God.
不管是谁干的总有另一个理由某种私人动机
Whoever did this has another motive, something personal.
不管是谁干的
Whoever did this...
他们都是在牵动所有的绳索
...they're pulling all the strings.
你爸爸就是这一切的原因
Your dad is the reason for all of this.
他就是当初我想这么做的原因
He's why I wanted to do this in the first place.
我从十二岁起就梦想着看到这场景
I've been dreaming about this since I was 12 years old.
这他妈的是怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on
快跑
Go, go, go
趴下现在就趴下
Get down  Get down now
让我看到你的双手
OFFICER 2: Let me see your hands
别别别住手
No  No, no, stop
不要天啊
No  God
不许动一不 不
Freeze  No, no
不
No
把它放下
Put it down
放下武器
Lower your weapon
开枪
Fire
不要
No